[
  {
    "name": "Maths",
    "id": "food",
    "theme": "green",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "What is the value of sin(30)",
        "options": [
          "1/2",
          "3/2",
          "1/3",
          "1/4"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Who was the one to discover zero?",
        "options": [
          "Newton",
          "Jeff Goldblum",
          "Aaryabhatta",
          "Shrinivasan Ramanujahn"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      }

    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Science",
    "id": "knowledge",
    "theme": "yellow",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If a 5,000 coupon bond has a coupon rate of 13 percent, then the coupon payment every year is ___",
        "options": [
          "650",
          "1,300",
          "None of These",
          "130"
        ],
        "answer": 0
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The average of first 50 natural numbers is ",
        "options": [
          "25.30",
          "25.50",
          "25.00",
          "12.25"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "History",
    "id": "history",
    "theme": "blue",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "The number of 3-digit numbers divisible by 6, is",
        "options": [
          "149",
          "166",
          "150",
          "151"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Average of three person’s age is 9 years. Find the sum of there age",
        "options": [
          "18",
          "21",
          "24",
          "27"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Which number is missing? 1, 9, 25, 49, (?)",
        "options": [
          "121",
          "81",
          "16",
          "169"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Which least number should be added to 2600 to make it a perfect square?",
        "options": [
          "3",
          "39",
          "1",
          "5"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "A clock seen through a mirror shows 8 o’clock. What is the correct time?",
        "options": [
          "8:00",
          "4:00",
          "12.20",
          "12.40"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If David’s age is 27 years old in 2011. What was his age in 2003?",
        "options": [
          "17 years",
          "37 years",
          "20 years",
          "19 years"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "What is 7% equal to?",
        "options": [
          "0.007",
          "0.07",
          "0.7",
          "7"
        ],
        "answer": 2
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "0.05 × 0.09 × 5 = ___",
        "options": [
          "0.005",
          "0.0225",
          "0.025",
          "0.225"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "If 5 boys take 7 hours to pack 35 cartoons, then how many boys can pack 65 cartoons in 3 hours?",
        "options": [
          "26",
          "39",
          "45",
          "None of These"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "106 × 106 – 94 × 94 = ?",
        "options": [
          "2004",
          "2400",
          "1904",
          "1906"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  },
  {
    "name": "Programming Fundamentals",
    "id": "food",
    "theme": "green",
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "Who is father of C Language?",
        "options": [
         " Bjarne Stroustrup",
          "James A. Gosling",
          "Dennis Ritchie",
          "Dr. E.F. Codd"
        ],
        "answer": 3
      },
      {
        "type": "single-select",
        "question": "C Language developed at _________?",
        "options": [
          "AT & T's Bell Laboratories of USA in 1972",


         " AT & T's Bell Laboratories of USA in 1970",

         " Sun Microsystems in 1973",

          "Cambridge University in 1972"
        ],
        "answer": 1
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "solved": "false"
  }

]
